

SOFT SKILLS

- Self-driven
- Flexibility

HARD SKILLS



SQL

[SQL Server, PostgreSQL]



Python

[Django, UnitTest]



HTML



[Bootstrap]



Learning:



React

GITHUB



https://github.com/maurumblr

LANGUAGES



Native



upper intermediate b2

CONTACT



Córdoba, Argentina



mfara.mf@gmail.com



www.linkedin.com/in/mauriciofara/? locale=en_US

Mauricio Fara

PROFILE

I'm a full-stack developer committed to provide fast and functional solutions. I recently worked as a BI back-end developer. I approach different issues with critical thinking to find efficient solutions. I am always ready for new challenges.

WORK EXPERIENCE

BI developer

Assist Card | July 2021- April 2022

- Leadership of the BI back-end team made up of 6 members.
- Analysis and prioritization of business requirements.
- ETL analysis and development in SSIS.
- Control and fixing of daily data extraction processes in production environment.

Technologies: SQL Server, SQL Server Integration Services (SSIS), SQL Server Analysis Services (SSAS), SQL Server Reporting Services (SSRS), Tableau, PowerBI

BI Consultant (Client: AssistCard)

CoreBI | December 2020 - July 2021

- ETL analysis and development in SSIS.
- Follow up of data extraction processes.

Technologies: SQL Server, SQL Server Integration Services (SSIS), SQL Server Analysis Services (SSAS), SQL Server Reporting Services (SSRS), Tableau, PowerBI

E-commerce manager

Majul Hogar S.A | April 2016 - December 2020

- Management of the online sales channel.
- Product catalog, review, stock rotation and product photography.
- Monitoring customer service.
- Logistics coordination for national shipments.
- Monitoring of technical problems affecting the company's image.

Technologies: SQL Server, Aikon ERP

EDUCATION

Facultad Regional Buenos Aires - UTN Diploma in Django framework | 2022

Facultad Regional Córdoba - UTN

Computer Programming | 2020 - 2022

Facultad de Ciencias Agropecuarias - UNC

Bachelor's Degree in Agricultural Engineering | 2013 - 2020 (incomplete)